# +358(0)403615047 Espoo, Finland sanzharfromkz@gmail.com

# Sanzhar Yeleuov

Cyber Security Engineer

Security engineer with solid theoretical background and up-to-date practical experience acquired during 1 year in academia and 2 years of work in industry leading companies of Kazakhstan and Russia. Co-author of an article accepted to appear in IEEE Transactions on Mobile Computing. Conducted internal and external penetration tests for private and government sectors. Developed and integrated automation tools, which allowed to boost the security testing process by doubling range of vulnerabilities covered automatically.

#### **EDUCATION**

#### Ulsan National Institute of Science and Technology (UNIST)

**SEP 2016 — AUG 2020** 

Bachelor of Computer Science

Ulsan, South Korea

GitHub: yelsanya

LinkedIn: yelsanya

Global Unistar Scholarship (Full tuition + 300,000 KRW/month)

**Erasmus Mundus Joint Master Degree in Security and Cloud Computing (SECCLO)** 

**SEP 2022 — AUG 2024 (expected)** 

Master's of Computer Science

Espoo, Finland + TBD

Erasmus Mundus Scholarship (Full tuition + 1000 Euro/month)

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# **Security Testing Engineer**

OCT 2021 — SEP 2022

R-VISION

Moscow, Russia

- Penetration tests of internal products
- Automatization and integration of security checks
- Internal security trainings

#### **Information Security Engineer**

**DEC 2020 — AUG 2021** 

KazDream Technologies

Nur-Sultan, Kazakhstan

- · Internal and external penetration tests
- Desktop application security audit

Research Assistant
UNIST Computer Systems Security Lab

APR 2019 — JAN 2020

Ulsan, South Korea

- · Conducted research in a Computer Systems Security Lab under direction of Prof. Hyungon Moon
- · Publications:
  - "Ambassy: A Runtime Framework to Delegate Trusted Applications in an ARM/FPGA Hybrid System" IEEE Transactions on Mobile Computing

#### **PROJECTS**

# Chat

C++ (multi threading, thread pool and sockets)

Multi-user client-server chat with command line interface.

#### Impact of COVID-19 on economics

JavaScript, Vega-Lite

• Interactive web application that allows to visualize data of various countries related to COVID-19 and economic indicators such as GPD and stock prices on different time slices

# Mouse logger

Linux kernel (Android), bash

Script that identifies position of the mouse cursor and then tracks its movement

#### Credentials retriever

Windows, C, dll

· Implemented dll file which on load starts to look for the credentials in the memory of the process

# Charity website (production)

NodeJS, ReactJS, MySQL, HTML

• Simple website with ads, where all monetized money sent to selected charity organizations divided proportionally to peoples choice

# **INTERESTS**